export const chapter7StudyData = [
  // Key Terms
  {
    id: "KT701",
    front: "algorithm",
    back: "problem-solving strategy characterized by a specific set of instructions"
  },
  {
    id: "KT702",
    front: "analytical intelligence",
    back: "aligned with academic problem solving and computations"
  },
  {
    id: "KT703",
    front: "anchoring bias",
    back: "faulty heuristic in which you fixate on a single aspect of a problem to find a solution"
  },
  {
    id: "KT704",
    front: "artificial concept",
    back: "concept that is defined by a very specific set of characteristics"
  },
  {
    id: "KT705",
    front: "availability heuristic",
    back: "faulty heuristic in which you make a decision based on information readily available to you"
  },
  {
    id: "KT706",
    front: "cognition",
    back: "thinking, including perception, learning, problem solving, judgment, and memory"
  },
  {
    id: "KT707",
    front: "cognitive psychology",
    back: "field of psychology dedicated to studying every aspect of how people think"
  },
  {
    id: "KT708",
    front: "cognitive script",
    back: "set of behaviors that are performed the same way each time; also referred to as an event schema"
  },
  {
    id: "KT709",
    front: "concept",
    back: "category or grouping of linguistic information, objects, ideas, or life experiences"
  },
  {
    id: "KT710",
    front: "confirmation bias",
    back: "faulty heuristic in which you focus on information that confirms your beliefs"
  },
  {
    id: "KT711",
    front: "convergent thinking",
    back: "providing correct or established answers to problems"
  },
  {
    id: "KT712",
    front: "creative intelligence",
    back: "ability to produce new products, ideas, or inventing a new, novel solution to a problem"
  },
  {
    id: "KT713",
    front: "creativity",
    back: "ability to generate, create, or discover new ideas, solutions, and possibilities"
  },
  {
    id: "KT714",
    front: "crystallized intelligence",
    back: "characterized by acquired knowledge and the ability to retrieve it"
  },
  {
    id: "KT715",
    front: "cultural intelligence",
    back: "ability with which people can understand and relate to those in another culture"
  },
  {
    id: "KT716",
    front: "divergent thinking",
    back: "ability to think \"outside the box\" to arrive at novel solutions to a problem"
  },
  {
    id: "KT717",
    front: "dysgraphia",
    back: "learning disability that causes extreme difficulty in writing legibly"
  },
  {
    id: "KT718",
    front: "dyslexia",
    back: "common learning disability in which letters are not processed properly by the brain"
  },
  {
    id: "KT719",
    front: "emotional intelligence",
    back: "ability to understand emotions and motivations in yourself and others"
  },
  {
    id: "KT720",
    front: "event schema",
    back: "set of behaviors that are performed the same way each time; also referred to as a cognitive script"
  },
  {
    id: "KT721",
    front: "fluid intelligence",
    back: "ability to see complex relationships and solve problems"
  },
  {
    id: "KT722",
    front: "Flynn effect",
    back: "observation that each generation has a significantly higher IQ than the previous generation"
  },
  {
    id: "KT723",
    front: "functional fixedness",
    back: "inability to see an object as useful for any other use other than the one for which it was intended"
  },
  {
    id: "KT724",
    front: "grammar",
    back: "set of rules that are used to convey meaning through the use of a lexicon"
  },
  {
    id: "KT725",
    front: "heuristic",
    back: "mental shortcut that saves time when solving a problem"
  },
  {
    id: "KT726",
    front: "hindsight bias",
    back: "belief that the event just experienced was predictable, even though it really wasn't"
  },
  {
    id: "KT727",
    front: "intelligence quotient (also, IQ)",
    back: "score on a test designed to measure intelligence"
  },
  {
    id: "KT728",
    front: "language",
    back: "communication system that involves using words to transmit information from one individual to another"
  },
  {
    id: "KT729",
    front: "lexicon",
    back: "the words of a given language"
  },
  {
    id: "KT730",
    front: "mental set",
    back: "continually using an old solution to a problem without results"
  },
  {
    id: "KT731",
    front: "morpheme",
    back: "smallest unit of language that conveys some type of meaning"
  },
  {
    id: "KT732",
    front: "Multiple Intelligences Theory",
    back: "Gardner's theory that each person possesses at least eight types of intelligence"
  },
  {
    id: "KT733",
    front: "natural concept",
    back: "mental groupings that are created \"naturally\" through your experiences"
  },
  {
    id: "KT734",
    front: "norming",
    back: "administering a test to a large population so data can be collected to reference the normal scores for a population and its groups"
  },
  {
    id: "KT735",
    front: "overgeneralization",
    back: "extension of a rule that exists in a given language to an exception to the rule"
  },
  {
    id: "KT736",
    front: "phoneme",
    back: "basic sound unit of a given language"
  },
  {
    id: "KT737",
    front: "practical intelligence",
    back: "aka \"street smarts\""
  },
  {
    id: "KT738",
    front: "problem-solving strategy",
    back: "method for solving problems"
  },
  {
    id: "KT739",
    front: "prototype",
    back: "best representation of a concept"
  },
  {
    id: "KT740",
    front: "range of reaction",
    back: "each person's response to the environment is unique based on his or her genetic make-up"
  },
  {
    id: "KT741",
    front: "representative bias",
    back: "faulty heuristic in which you stereotype someone or something without a valid basis for your judgment"
  },
  {
    id: "KT742",
    front: "representative sample",
    back: "subset of the population that accurately represents the general population"
  },
  {
    id: "KT743",
    front: "role schema",
    back: "set of expectations that define the behaviors of a person occupying a particular role"
  },
  {
    id: "KT744",
    front: "schema (plural = schemata)",
    back: "mental construct consisting of a cluster or collection of related concepts"
  },
  {
    id: "KT745",
    front: "semantics",
    back: "process by which we derive meaning from morphemes and words"
  },
  {
    id: "KT746",
    front: "standard deviation",
    back: "measure of variability that describes the difference between a set of scores and their mean"
  },
  {
    id: "KT747",
    front: "standardization",
    back: "method of testing in which administration, scoring, and interpretation of results are consistent"
  },
  {
    id: "KT748",
    front: "syntax",
    back: "manner by which words are organized into sentences"
  },
  {
    id: "KT749",
    front: "trial and error",
    back: "problem-solving strategy in which multiple solutions are attempted until the correct one is found"
  },
  {
    id: "KT750",
    front: "triarchic theory of intelligence",
    back: "Sternberg's theory of intelligence; three facets of intelligence: practical, creative, and analytical"
  },
  {
    id: "KT751",
    front: "working backwards",
    back: "heuristic in which you begin to solve a problem by focusing on the end result"
  },
  // Review Questions
  {
    id: "R701",
    front: "Cognitive psychology is the branch of psychology that focuses on the study of ________.",
    back: "human thinking"
  },
  {
    id: "R702",
    front: "Which of the following is an example of a prototype for the concept of leadership on an athletic team?",
    back: "the team captain"
  },
  {
    id: "R703",
    front: "Which of the following is an example of an artificial concept?",
    back: "a triangle's area"
  },
  {
    id: "R704",
    front: "An event schema is also known as a cognitive ________.",
    back: "script"
  },
  {
    id: "R705",
    front: "________ provides general principles for organizing words into meaningful sentences.",
    back: "Syntax"
  },
  {
    id: "R706",
    front: "________ are the smallest unit of language that carry meaning.",
    back: "Morphemes"
  },
  {
    id: "R707",
    front: "The meaning of words and phrases is determined by applying the rules of ________.",
    back: "semantics"
  },
  {
    id: "R708",
    front: "________ is (are) the basic sound units of a spoken language.",
    back: "Phonemes"
  },
  {
    id: "R709",
    front: "A specific formula for solving a problem is called ________.",
    back: "an algorithm"
  },
  {
    id: "R710",
    front: "A mental shortcut in the form of a general problem-solving framework is called ________.",
    back: "a heuristic"
  },
  {
    id: "R711",
    front: "Which type of bias involves becoming fixated on a single trait of a problem?",
    back: "anchoring bias"
  },
  {
    id: "R712",
    front: "Which type of bias involves relying on a false stereotype to make a decision?",
    back: "representative bias"
  },
  {
    id: "R713",
    front: "Fluid intelligence is characterized by ________.",
    back: "being able to see complex relationships and solve problems"
  },
  {
    id: "R714",
    front: "Which of the following is not one of Gardner's Multiple Intelligences?",
    back: "creative"
  },
  {
    id: "R715",
    front: "Which theorist put forth the triarchic theory of intelligence?",
    back: "Sternberg"
  },
  {
    id: "R716",
    front: "When you are examining data to look for trends, which type of intelligence are you using most?",
    back: "analytical"
  },
  {
    id: "R717",
    front: "In order for a test to be normed and standardized it must be tested on ________.",
    back: "a representative sample"
  },
  {
    id: "R718",
    front: "The mean score for a person with an average IQ is ________.",
    back: "100"
  },
  {
    id: "R719",
    front: "Who developed the IQ test most widely used today?",
    back: "David Wechsler"
  },
  {
    id: "R720",
    front: "The DSM-5 now uses ________ as a diagnostic label for what was once referred to as mental retardation.",
    back: "intellectual disability"
  },
  {
    id: "R721",
    front: "Where does high intelligence come from?",
    back: "both A and B (genetics and environment)"
  },
  {
    id: "R722",
    front: "Arthur Jensen believed that ________.",
    back: "genetics was solely responsible for intelligence"
  },
  {
    id: "R723",
    front: "What is a learning disability?",
    back: "a neurological disorder"
  },
  {
    id: "R724",
    front: "Which of the following statements is true?",
    back: "There are many factors working together to influence an individual's intelligence level."
  }
];